Guide to the Charles Barber papers related to Alexander Siloti M2112
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Music Scores, 1902-1942, undated
  - Liszt, Erstes Konzert fur Pianoforte und Orchester (photocopy), (undated) (Flat-box 12, Folder 10)
  - Liszt, Il Penseroso, 1923 (Flat-box 12, Folder 11)
  - Liszt, Klavier-Konzert NR. 2 A-Dur (some notes glued in) (pencil and ink annotations), 1926 (Flat-box 12, Folder 12)
  - Liszt, Konzert 1 (some notes glued in), 1932 (Flat-box 12, Folder 13)
  - Liszt, Les jeux d’eaux a la villa d’Este No. 4, 1924 (Flat-box 13, Folder 1)
  - Liszt, Les jeux d’eaux a la villa d’Este No. 4, 1924 (Flat-box 13, Folder 2)
  - Liszt, Notturno No. 3 (pencil annotations), undated (Flat-box 13, Folder 3)
  - Liszt, Notturno Nr. 3, undated (Flat-box 13, Folder 4)
  - Liszt, Orage (1re Annee), 1909 (Flat-box 13, Folder 5)
  - Liszt, Pensees des Morts, undated (Flat-box 13, Folder 6)
  - Liszt, Polonaise No. 2 in E, 1930 (Flat-box 13, Folder 7)
  - Liszt, Rhapsodie hongroise No. 12 (pencil and ink annotations), 1914 (Flat-box 13, Folder 8)
  - Liszt, Rhapsodie Hongroise No. 14, undated (Flat-box 13, Folder 9)
  - Liszt, Sposalizo, 1924 (Flat-box 13, Folder 10)
  - Liszt, Sonate (photocopy), (undated) (Flat-box 13, Folder 11)
  - Liszt, St. Francis de Paule marchant sur les flots, 1923 (Flat-box 13, Folder 12)
  - Liszt, Sursum Corda, 1924 (Flat-box 13, Folder 13)
  - Paginini-Liszt, Etude No. 6 Theme with Variations, 1942 (Flat-box 13, Folder 14)
  - Luigini, Ballet Egyptien No. 1, 1902 (Flat-box 13, Folder 15)
  - Mendelssohn, Scherzo (photocopy), (undated) (Flat-box 13, Folder 16)
  - Mozart, Variations (“Ah! Vous dirai-je, maman”) C Major, 1924 (Flat-box 13, Folder 17)
  - Rachmaninoff, Preludes op. 23, V. – VI. (pencil annotations), undated (Flat-box 14, Folder 1)
  - Rachmaninoff, Italian Polka (photocopy), (undated) (Flat-box 14, Folder 2)
  - Rachmaninoff, Melodie, Op. 3, No. 23 (photocopy), (undated) (Flat-box 14, Folder 3)
  - Rachmaninoff, Romance (In the Silence of Night), Op. 4, No. 3 (photocopy), (1929) (Flat-box 14, Folder 4)
  - Riabinin, Fantaisie (handwritten), undated (Flat-box 14, Folder 5)
  - Rubinstein, Lezginka (Dance from the Opera “The Demon”) (photocopy), (1949) (Flat-box 14, Folder 6)
    Includes correspondence from Maria Siloti and a photocopy of a Russian article about Siloti's 120th birthday.
  - Rubinstein, Troisieme Barcarolle, 1904 (Flat-box 14, Folder 7)
  - Rubinstein, Troisieme Barcarolle Op. 50 (photocopy), (1904) (Flat-box 14, Folder 8)
  - Rubinstein, Valse-Caprice, undated (Flat-box 14, Folder 9)
  - Saint-Saens, Le Cygne, 1924 (Flat-box 14, Folder 10)
  - Schlozer, Etude Op. 1, No. 2 (photocopy), (1929) (Flat-box 14, Folder 11)
  - Schubert, Impromptu (G Major) (photocopy), (undated) (Flat-box 14, Folder 12)
  - Schubert’s Weerke, Serie IX (phantasie, impromptu, und andere stucke fur piano), undated (Flat-box 14, Folder 13)
  - Siloti, Polka Russe, 1921 (Flat-box 14, Folder 14)
  - Siloti, Transcriptions for the Young (photocopy), (1922) (Flat-box 14, Folder 15)
  - Tausig, Hungarian Dances (photocopy), (undated) (Flat-box 14, Folder 16)
  - Tchaikovsky, Concerto No. 1 in B Minor for Pianoforte; arr., 1905 (Flat-box 15, Folder 1)
  - Tchaikovsky, Piano Concerto No. 2, undated (Flat-box 15, Folder 2)
  - Tchaikovsky, Trio fur Pianoforte, Violine, Violoncell, undated (Flat-box 15, Folder 3)
    Includes correspondence from Maria Siloti, 1988
  - Vieuxtemps, Concerto 4me (orch parts), undated (Flat-box 15, Folder 4)
  - Vieuxtemps, Grand Concerto No. IV, undated (Flat-box 15, Folder 5)
  - Vivaldi, Concerto in D Minor RV 565 (photocopy), (undated) (Flat-box 15, Folder 6)